(Penny:)about a killer gorilla.
(Penny:)After I did it,
I felt so ashamed.
(Penny:)Thankfully,
that thing never came out.
(Sheldon:)I've seen that.
(Sheldon:)-Yeah. Serial Apeist.
(Sheldon:)Howard found it online
the day we met you.
(Penny:)-Oh, God.
-l mean, it was literally
(Sheldon:)the moment you walked out the door.
(Sheldon:)But I see the type of personal
revelations you're going for.
(Sheldon:)Okay, here's one I thought
I'd take to the grave.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)A while back,
YouTube changed its user interface
(Sheldon:)from a star-based rating system
to a thumbs-up rating system.
(Sheldon:)I tell people I'm okay with it,
but I'm really not.
(Penny:)-That's your big revelation?
-Yes.